Guide to the Bettie Lee Yerka papers, 1963-2000.
Yerka, Bettie Lee
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Bettie Lee Yerka papers, 1963-2000.
23-24-3847
Bettie Lee Yerka
1 cubic foot.
Printed Materials, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes publications, subject and project files pertaining to nutrition programs such as Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program (EFNEP) and Yerka's career in the College of Human Ecology.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor, Dept. of Policy Analysis and Management, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes publications, subject and project files pertaining to nutrition programs such as Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program (EFNEP) and Yerka's career in the College of Human Ecology.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Yerka, Bettie Lee; Cornell University--Faculty.; Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program (U.S.); New York State College of Human Ecology.Dept. of Policy Analysis and Management.
Subjects:
Nutrition extension work--New York (State).; Children--Nutrition.; Nutritional science--Study and teaching.; Nutrition policy.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Publications, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Publications, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Publications and Annual Report, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Publications, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Building Blocks for Toddlers- Final Report, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Healthy Families- Final Report, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Reports- County Home Demonstration, 1960s (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Department of Human Service Studies, 1983-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Expanded Nutrition Education Program (ENEP)- correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Home Economics Initiatives, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Evaluation- The Textile and Apparel Outlook, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Evaluation- Clothing Construction Program, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Evaluation in Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1981-1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Evaluations- Local Programs, 1974-1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Evaluation- Local Program- Appraisal of Evidence Methodology, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Evaluation Plans- Samples, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Extension Program Reviews, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Evaluation Planning, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Program Development Planning, 1976-1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Program Development and Evaluation, 1983-1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Marketing Extension- Program Impacts, 1980-1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Planning- Support for Staff/Extension Administration, 1982-1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Issue Focus Programming, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Statewide Impact Studies- For Evaluation Study + USDA, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Statewide Program Evaluations- Samples, 1989-2000 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Northeast Workshops; Northeast and Natural Interest in Accountability and Evaluation, 1979-1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Regional Program Committee Workshops, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Conference- NYS Home Economics, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Hatch Project, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Parent Education Video Series, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)